https://www.tedjob.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of the Internet sites, applications and services ("Services") that are operated by, controlled by or are affiliate with Jobelephant.com, Inc. This Privacy Policy does not govern our use of any information you provide to us when you call us, write to us, or communicate with us in any manner other than through the Services. Because the Internet is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, and held in countries (including the United States) other than the one in which you reside. By using the Services, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Our Services contain links to other web sites over which we have no control. Jobelephant.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. We also do not control the data use practices of employers or others who may access your information on this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and opt- out choices of those third parties so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.
Information We Automatically Collect
We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use the Services (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as "Usage Data"). For example, each time you visit the Services we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit.
We will use such Usage Data to diagnose problems with our servers and software, to administer the Services, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party advertising networks and servers will also provide us reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked on the Services in a manner that does not identify personally any individual.
Information You Choose To Submit
You can visit the Services without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as "Personal Information"). If, however, you wish to register to become a member of the Services, you are required to provide certain Personal Information, and we ask that you also provide a user name and password. We use your Personal Information to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve our Services, and to contact you from time to time about us, and our products and services.
You may also choose to submit additional information about yourself by which someone could not personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as "Non-Personal Information"). We may also collect additional information about you when you visit certain features of the Services or the pages of certain of our partners when you interact with offers and advertisements, when you contact us for support, or when you log into the Services with your account. Finally, you may choose to submit other information, Personal and Non-Personal,that you would like to share with other users of the Services (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as "Shared Information").
Our Information Sharing Practices
(a) Generally. Except as otherwise described in this section of our Privacy Policy, we will never share your Usage Data, Personal Information, Non-Personal Information, or Shared Information (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as "User Information") with any third party without your permission.
(b) Aggregated Data. From time to time, we may share aggregated User Information with third parties. We will not share any aggregated data, however, in manner that would enable the recipient to personally identify you.
(c) Service Providers. From time to time, we may enter into relationships with third parties who provide services to us (e.g., data management and storage services or credit card processing services). In those circumstances, we disclose User Information that is necessary for such service providers to perform those services and require that they maintain the confidentiality of such User Information.
(d) Other Disclosure Scenarios. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any User Information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Services' infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (4) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy); and (5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity.
Advertising
We may use other companies under agreements with us to serve advertisements when you visit and use the Services. These companies may collect and use click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over during your visits to the Services and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie, a third party web beacon and/or pixel tags to collect this information. None of them collect any personal information from your computer, such as your e-mail address. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.
Modifying and Deleting Your Personal Information
If you would like to modify or delete from our database any User Information you previously submitted to us, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. Please note that any User Information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your request, and that if you delete certain information you may not be able to order services in the future without re-submitting such information. Also, please note that we will maintain User Information in our database whenever we are required to do so by law.
Security
We have implemented reasonable measures to help protect your User Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your User Information, we cannot guarantee its security.
Children's Privacy
We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. The Services are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Services to children under the age of 13.
Changes
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If under any such update we make any material change to the way in which we treat your User Information, we will inform you of such change via email or by posting a notice on relevant areas of the Services. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date set forth therein.
Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at privacy@jobelephant.com.
Post a Job
My Account
Employer Sign Up
Employer Login
By continuing to use our site, you agree to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.
Learn more about how we use cookies by reviewing our Cookie Policy.
